Literatura de Cordel collection, 1918-1995
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Religious Stories., 1918-1995.
  - Title: A presença do Papa no Brasil Author: Severino Sertanejo Publisher: unknown., ca. 1980s. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Title: A paixão de Cristo Author: Waldeck Oliveira Publisher: Grupo Acauã., after 1960. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Title: O Papa no Piauí Author: Juvenal Evangelista Publisher: unknown., 01/07/80. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Title: O Papa nas Malvinas fim da guerra Author: Ferreira Poeta da Vila Publisher: João Luiz Ramão ?., ca. 1980s. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Title: Padre José de Anchieta Author: Homero do Rêgo Barros Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic HOMERO., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Title: Papa do povo João Paulo II Author: Antonio Palmeira da Silva Publisher: unknown Other: 2nd edição., Junho de 1980. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Title: O Padre Cícero em Roma fez ele um mudo-surdo falar Author: Manoel Caboclo e Silva Publisher: unknown., 11/9/79. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Title: A profecia do Pe Cícero sobre o Juazeiro Author: unknown Publisher: Lira Nordestina., 10/08/82. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - ca. 1980. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1981. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 10 de Julho de 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Visita do Santo Papa ao Recife Author: Homero de Rêgo Barros Publisher: H. R. Barros Other: acrostic HOMERO., 1980. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A vinda do Santo Papa ao Brasil Author: Olegario Fernandes Publisher: Folheteria Boa Vista., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A visita de sua santidade o Papa João Paulo II ao Rio e ao Brasil Author: Expedito F. Silva Publisher: Folheteria Boa Vista., ca. 1980s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Trezena do insigne portugues Santo Antonio Author: unknown Publisher: José Bernardo da Silva., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Traços biográficos de São Francisco de Assis Author: Manoel Barauna Neto Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O terrível castigo para os ladrões que foram roubar Frei Damião Author: Romildo Santos Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: Casa das Crianças de Olinda., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Testamento de Judas oferta da AVPPFC aos amigos de Juazeiro do Norte Author: Pedro Bandeira Illustrator: signed FRANCORLD Publisher: unknown., 9/4/1976. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Vida completa do Padre Cicero seus milagres e morte Author: Manoel Camilo dos Santos Publisher: M. C. dos Santos Other: acrostic MANOEL CAMILO., 21/6/1956. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O velho que enganou o Diabo Author: José Antonio Torres (Zé Catolé) Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: J. Borges Place: Bezerros., 18/03/81. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A vós de Frei Damião Author: Ivo Luiz Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A verdade sobre a divórcio Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic RODOLFO., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Viagem por um milagre do Padre Cícero Romão Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Publisher: Tipografia Pontes Other: acrostic AALVES., ca. 1980s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A verdadeira profecia e almanaque do profeta Frei Vidal da Penha para o ano de 1975 Author: Caetano Cosme da Silva Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic CAETANO., ca. 1975. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O atentado do Papa abalou o mundo inteiro Author: Leonardo Rodrigues dos Santos Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Os sinais do fim do mundo e as três pedras de Carvão Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A santa que falou profetizando em Minas Gerais de 1977 até 1999 Author: José Costa Leite Publisher: J. C. Leite Other: acrostic COSTALEITE., after 1977. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A santificação, a oração e a profecia do Padre Cícero Romão Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: J. C. Leite., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: As sete espadas de dores da Santa Virgem Maria Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: Tip Pontes., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O Satanás reclamando o corrução de hoje em dia Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: A Voz da Poesia Nordestina Other: acrostic COSTALEITE., ca. 1970s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Satanás trabalhando no roçado de São Pedro Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: MEC/PRONASEC RURAL, UFPb FUNAPE Other: acrostic COSTALEITE., 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O ateu que virou Jegue Author: Antonio Lucena Illustrator: signed LUCENA 1982 Publisher: unknown. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Antonio Conselheiro o santo guerreiro de Canudos Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Illustrator: signed DILA Publisher: PRONASEC RURAL, UFPb FUNAPE Other: acrostic RODOLFO., 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A tentativa de assassinato do Papa João de Deus Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: Gráfica Redil Other: 1st edition., maio 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A triste condenação do bom Padre Reginaldo Velozo do Morro da Conceição Author: Antônio do Morro Illustrator: José Costa Leite signed JCL Publisher: Fundação Casa das Crianças de Olinda., 29 de junho de 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Septenario de Nossa Senhora do destêrro Author: unknown Illustrator: signed STENIO Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Sermão profético Padre Cicero Romão Author: João Ferreira Lima Publisher: unknown., 19/08/82. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A santificação do Pe Cicero Author: unknown Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O Satanás procurando emprego Author: José Camilo da Silva Illustrator: José Costa Leite signed JCL Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic JOSECAMILO., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O sonho de Frei Damião e a carta profetizando o futuro Author: João Fernandes de Oliveira Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A 2a queixa de Satanaz a cristo sobre a corrução do mundo Author: José Vilanova Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic VILANOVA., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Todo sertanejo vive com fé em Frei Damião, tudo eu sei ninguem me ensina Author: José Costa Leite Publisher: A Voz da Poesia Nordestina., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O ladrão que quis roubar na matriz de Juazeiro e morreu Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista., 23/11/75. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Um natal em Caruaru Author: José Severino Cristovão Illustrator: signed VALERIO Publisher: Foletaria São Cristovão., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Advertisement for Volkswagen Caruaru Motor on rear wrapper and in final stanzas of poem.
  - Title: A vida de Buda em versos Author: J. Palmeira Guimarães Illustrator: signed MARCONI 77 Publisher: unknown., 1977. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: O menino que nasceu com a pintuara do cão Author: Manoel Caboclo e Silva Illustrator: signed A.M.S. Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A moça que virou cachorra Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic COSTALEITE., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    "Oração de São Jorge" in the shape of a cross on rear wrapper.
  - Title: O mundo evangelizado Author: Cícero Barros Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A moça que o Diabo tomou conta para a matar de fome Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista., 1977. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: O velho que se apaixonou por Santa Terezinha e morreu Donzelo Author: Raimundo Silva Illustrator: signed but illegible Publisher: Japeri Araújo? Place: São Paulo., 21 de maio de 1984. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Noite de Natal, desejo para você e para toda humanidade natal e ano novo com grande felicidade Author: Antonio Palmaeira da Silva (Poeta Motoqueiro) Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A moça que virou jumenta porque falou de Top Less com Frei Damião Author: José Francisco Borges Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., 1980s. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: O protestante que virou num urubu por que quis matar Frei Damião Author: Manoel Sarafim Illustrator: José Costa Leite signed JCL Publisher: unknown., 1970s. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A tragedia de Garanhuns ou a morte do Bispo Author: Severino Paulino Silva Publisher: other Other: acrostic, PAULINO., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Porque e que o mundo está assim tão atrapalhado Author: Manoel Camilo dos Santos Publisher: A "Estrella" da Poesia., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Tem Papa na área Author: Valdeck de Garanhuns Illustrator: José Costa Leite signed JCL Publisher: Tipografia da Casa das Crianças de Olinda., 1 de julho de 1980. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Os três fugitivos para o Egito Jesus, Maria e José Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed JOEL Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Other: acrostic AALVES., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: As professias do Padre Cícero Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: Biblioteca Nacional do Cordel Other: 5th edition., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Advertisement for "Refrigerante de Cajú, Cajuína São Geraldo" on rear wrapper.
  - Title: Os 4 sonhos reveladores do Padre Cícero Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista., Junho 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: O Padre Cícero e a cura de um louco 1926 Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Advertisement for "Banda Magazine" on rear wrapper.
  - Title: A romaria de Cícero Cary a Juazeiro do Padre Cícero 1990 Author: José Freitas de Souza Illustrator: Abraão Batista signed ABB Publisher: Lira Nordestina. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Visita a Juazeiro do Norte do presidente quem tem "aquilo" roxo Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista., 1991. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Segunda visita do Papa João Paulo II ao Brasil Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Other: acrostic AALVES., 1991. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Padre João Maria o Santo de Natal Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: Iaperi Araujo signed I. A. Publisher: Fundação José Augusto Other: acrostic AALVES., after 1960. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: II visita do Papa ao Brasil Author: Homero do Rêgo Barros Publisher: Fundação José Augusto., 1991. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A cidade Juazeiro do Padre Cícero Romão Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Other: acrostic AALVES., setembro de 1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Aviso misterioso da imagem da rosa mística que chorou lágrimas de sangue em Fortaleza Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista., 11/12/1990. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A carta de D. Bosco a força do oratório Author: Pedro Bandeira Illustrator: signed Zevli? Publisher: unknown., 1984. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: O beberrão que lutou com o Diabo Sexta Feira da Paixão Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed J.BARROS Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic, aalvess., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: O Satanaz reclamando a corrução de hoje em dia Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: O sonho de Nossa Senhora e a pedra cristalina Author: José Costa Leite Publisher: J.C. Leite., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A guerra do Juazeiro Author: Lino Felipe dos Santos Illustrator: Fco. Correia Lima Publisher: L. F. dos Santos., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Festa pra todos os santos Author: José Joel de Souza Publisher: J. J. de Souza., after 1970. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Hallyne, a mocinha atropelada e morta na Av. Odilon Aguiar em Tauá Author: Edson Massilon Mathias Publisher: unknown., ca. 1994. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Pe. Cícero e Juazeiro ontem e hoje Author: Jackson Pires Barbosa Illustrator: Luis Karimai Publisher: Gráfica Lira Nordestina., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: Judeus e católicos na ceia pascal cristã Author: Raimundo Santa Helena Publisher: R. Santa Helena., 31/12/1984. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A moça que se casou 14 vezes e continuou Donzela Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Other: acrostic AALVES., after 1960. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A mulher que dançou com o Diabo numa boate em Campina Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed LUCENA 1990 Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Other: acrostic AALVES. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Title: A vida de Pedro Cem Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed JOEL Publisher: Tip. Pontes Other: acrostic AALVES., 10 de julho de 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A vida de Dom Hélder, homenagem no seu 50 aniversário de ordenação sacerdotal Author: Antônio do Morro Illustrator: signed jawes 81 Publisher: Fundação Casa das Crianças de Olinda., 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Visita do Santo Papa ao Recife Author: Homero do Rêgo Barros Publisher: H. R. Barros Other: acrostic, HOMERO., 1980. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A vinda do Santo Papa ao Brasil Author: Olegario Fernandes da Silva Publisher: Folheteria Boa Vista., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A visita de sua santidade o Papa João Paulo II ao Rio e ao Brasil Author: Expedito F. Silva Publisher: E. F. Silva., after 1980. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Trezena do insigne portugues Santo Antonio Author: unknown Publisher: José Bernardo da Silva., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Traços Biográficos de São Francisco de Assis Author: Manoel Barauna Neto Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O terrível castigo para os ladrões que foram roubar Frei Damião Author: Romildo Santos Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: Casa das Crianças de Olinda., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Testamento de Judas, ofterta da AVPPFC aos amigos de Juazeiro do Norte Author: Pedro Bandeira Illustrator: signed FRANCORLD Publisher: unknown., 9/4/1976. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Advertisement for "Supermercados Brasil" on rear wrapper.
  - Title: Vida completa do Padre Cícero seus milagres e morte Author: Manoel Camilo dos Santos Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic, MANOEL CAMILO., 21/6/1956. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O velho que enganou o Diabo Author: José Antonio Torres Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: unknown., 18/08/81. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A vòs de Frei Damião Author: Ivo Luiz Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A verdade sobre a divórcio Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic, RODOLFO., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Viagem por um milagre do Padre Cícero Romão Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Publisher: Tipografia Pontes Other: acrostic, AALVES., ca. 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A verdadeira profecia e almanaque do profeta Frei Vidal da Penha para o ano de 1975 Author: Caetano Cosme da Silva Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic, CAETANO., ca. 1975. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A visita dos Romeiros como era antigamente Author: Manoel Caboclo e Silva Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O atentado do Papa abalou o mundo inteiro Author: Leonardo Rodrigues dos Santos Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Os sinais do fim do mundo e as três pedras de Carvão Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A santa que falou profetizando em Minas Gerais de 1977 até 1999 Author: José Costa Leite Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic COSTALEITE., after 1977. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A santificação, a oração e a profecia do Padre Cícero Romão Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic COSTALEITE., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: As sete espadas de dores da Santa Virgem Maria Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: Tip. Pontes., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O satanás reclamando a corrução de hoje em dia Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: signed JCL Publisher: A Voz da Poesia Nordestina Other: acrostic COSTALEITE., ca. 1975. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Satanás trabalhando no roçado de São Pedro Author: José Costa Leite Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: MEC/PRONASEC RURAL, UFPb FUNAPE Other: acrostic COSTALEITE., 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O ateu que virou jegue Author: Antônio Lucena Illustrator: signed Lucena 1982 Publisher: unknown Place: Campina Grande. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Antonio Conselheiro o Santo Guerreiro de Canudos Author: Rodolfo Coelho Cavalcante Illustrator: José Cavalcanti e Ferreira Dila signed DILA Publisher: MEC/PRONASEC RURAL, UFPb FUNAPE Other: acrostic RODOLFO., 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A tentativa de assassinato do Papa João de Deus Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: Gráfica Redil., 18 maio 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Advertisement for Café Itaytera
  - Title: A triste condenação do bom Padre Reginaldo Velozo do Morro da Conceição Author: Antônio do Morro Illustrator: José Costa Leite signed JCL Publisher: Fundação Casa das Crianças de Olinda., 29 de junho de 1981. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Septenario de Nossa Senhora do desterro Author: unknown Illustrator: signed Stênio Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Sermão Profético do Padre Cicero Romão Author: João Ferreira Lima Publisher: unknown., 19/08/82. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A santificação do Pe. Cicero Author: unknown Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    UCLA copy does not have a cover.
  - Title: O Satanàs procurando emprego Author: José Camilo da Silva Illustrator: José Costa Leite signed JCL Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic JOSECAMILO., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: O sonho de Frei Damião e a carta profetizando o futuro Author: João Fernandes de Oliveira Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic JOSECAMILO., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: A 2a queixa de Satanaz a cristo sobre a corrução do mundo Author: José Vilanova Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic VILANOVA., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: Todo sertanejo vive com fé em Frei Damião, tudo eu sei ninguem me ensina Author: José Costa Leite Publisher: A Voz da Poesia Nordestina., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Title: 125 natais e Casimiro Fernandes Author: Valdeck de Garanhuns Illustrator: V. de Garanhuns Publisher: unknown., dezembro de 1985. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: São Jorge, o santo guerreiro, nascimento, vida e morte Author: Gonçalo Ferreira da Silva Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: Tip. Pontes., after 1960. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Os mistérios da Macumba Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed JOEL Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Other: acrostic AALVES., Janeiro de 1985. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Morte e ambição Author: José Nunes Filho (Oiticica) Illustrator: signed J.BARROS Publisher: unknown., after 1960. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: A moça que virou corba e quiz engulir a mãe Author: Apolonio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed MS Publisher: unknown., after 1960. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: O sermão de meu padrinho no ano de 32 Author: Manoel Caboclo e Silva Publisher: unknown., ca. 1991. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Chico Bento e Padre Amaro Author: Moreira de Acopiara Publisher: unknown Place: Fortaleza Other: 1a edição., 11/89. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: ABC do fim do mundo Author: Roberto Francisco de O. Leite (Chico Leite) Publisher: Gráfica Correio do Sertão Place: Morro de Chapeu, BA., 20/07/1988. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Vida e luta de Chico Mendes Author: da Silva Publisher: unknown., after 1988. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Descrição dos festejos de sesquicentenário de nascimento do Padre Cícero 1844-1994 Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista., 24/3/1994. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: O sermão da catinga do Padre Cícero Romão Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista., 05/05/1995. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Saudadação ao Juazeiro do Norte Author: Patativa do Assaré Illustrator: Luis Karimai Publisher: Gráfica Lira Nordestina., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Homenagem ao Padre Cícero em seu sesquicentenário Author: Francisco Mateu Illustrator: signed HB Publisher: unknown., 24/03/1994. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Juazeiro do Norte terra do Padre Cicero Author: Danilo Lopes Ferreira Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., 1900s. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: A vinda de Jesus Author: Jotabê Illustrator: signed RENE Publisher: unknown., 03/93. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: 3a queixa do Satanás a Cristo Author: Lucas Evangelista Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown Other: acrostic EVANGELISTA., after 1960. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: O Rio e a Eco-92 o grande debate em defesa da vida Author: Manoel Santa Maria Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., ca. 1992. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Content regards the environment.
  - Title: Milagre na cidade santa Author: Gonçalo Ferreira da Silva Illustrator: signed ERIVALDO Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Visita à casa de cultura São Saruê Author: Durval Lobo Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., after 1980. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Cordel a vida de Jesus para crianças Author: Ana Maria de Santana Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., 01 de setembro de 1992. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Dos sermões à poesia Author: Geraldo Carvalho Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., after 1992. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Saudades de um(a) fã Author: Dico Ramos Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Image of Luiz Gonzago on the front wrapper.
  - Title: Encontro de uma coroa injurada com Santo Antonio da Barbalha Author: Abraão Batista Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: A. Batista., junho 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Advertisement for "aguardente de cana" on rear wrapper.
  - Title: Encontro de Tancredo com Pe. Cícero no céu Author: Pedro Bandeira Illustrator: signed Stenio Publisher: unknown., 5/85. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Encontro de Luiz Gonzaga com Padre Cícero no céu Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Illustrator: signed ERIVALDO Publisher: unknown., after 1989. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Estrondosa guerrilha professia de meu padrim Cícero Romão Author: João Pedro C. Neto Illustrator: signed ABB Publisher: unknown., agosto 1990. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: O misterioso marco do Pe. Cícero Romão Author: Pedro Bandeira Illustrator: signed but illegible Publisher: unknown., 06/08/1984. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Advertisement for bicycle repairs on rear wrapper.
  - Title: Meu ABC de cordel a Juazeiro do Norte Author: Paulo Nunes Batista Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Romaria e milagre do Padre Cicero Romão Author: Apolônio Alves dos Santos Publisher: A. A. dos Santos Other: acrostic AALVES., janeiro de 1989. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: Cordeiro para São João é o cordeiro da paz Author: Joel B. de Amorim Illustrator: signed J.BORGES Publisher: unknown., after 1985. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Image of a voting ballot on rear wrapper.
  - Title: Irmã Dulce merece o prêmio nobel Author: José Neves Publisher: unknown Other: signed JNEVES., after 1960. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: A volta do padre Cicero e o aviso da bomba atômica Author: José Carlos C. Filho Publisher: unknown., after 1950. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Title: O Satanás resolveu falar com Frei Damião Author: Manoel Caboclo e Silva Illustrator: unsigned Publisher: unknown., 20/07/89. (Box 5, Folder 4)